Winston reporting
I didn't forget about you I stopped you
once I can do it again
a giant gorilla just like in those old
video games I did that a lot
kenji this is just like old times our
paths cross for now as to the future we
shall see
I always liked working with you Winston
no awkward small talk always liked
working with you too
you have great sense of humor
Winston how's it hanging um okay I guess
we got this big mission coming up it oh
I get it
I love your glasses so cute oh um thanks
I like yours too
we should compare notes sometime that
would be great what's your opinion on
the Tobel Steen's gravitational models
Vinson are you experiencing any issues
with your genetic therapy other than a
crippling addiction to a peanut butter
Teli fee if she's ever in gibraltar she
should look me up if you would be
honored to be able to meet such an
accomplished scientist and a member of
overwatch
Farra your mother was a hero to me to
all of us you probably knew her better
than me
or Winston asked hideaway so he doesn't
scare the children I don't even think
children are afraid of you
huh Winston heats up to us to keep our
comrades safe I'll be right behind you
sir
my job do you someone has to
someone's going to put a stop to your
illegal activities you're one to talk
you and your friends are breaking the
law same as me
Winston are you still use a maxi Lee
feather duster of a gun why don't you
come over here and ask that again
any adjustments to your chrono
accelerator I think just kidding Winston
it works great
Oh Winston got you favor for the last
time no more bananas
Winston you're an animal empirical
evidence suggests I'm a real animal
Winston your gun is so cute you should
try playing with some real firepower I
like to leave the heavy lifting to the
professionals
don't mess with my glasses
you stay away from my computer systems
tracer no